Since I was little,
my dad has always been my hero.
He always managed to find a way to be
there
whenever I needed him.
He supported me as I chased my dreams.
He gave me the wedding I'd always
wanted. And now he's helped me unlock
the door to our very [music] first home.
At every milestone,
he was there.
Truly there for me.
Even now, he still never fails to show
up.
And I can almost hear him saying, "It's
okay. Baba is here [music] whenever I
need him."
Because of legacy settlement option, his
love continues to guide me, even years
after he's gone.
And now I'll do the same to make sure I
can be there for my child even when I
[music] no longer can.
Legacy settlement [music]
option. Let your love live on into the
next generation.